ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
我和黑袍纠察队
Me and the Boys,
我们都准备好了
we're all set up.
只需要你下令
May I please have a green light?
不能致残 施以酷刑
No maiming or torture
或者把人放在火上烧
or setting anyone on fire.
ShinY
深影
■
ShinY
深影
■
翻译：  小鸡吃小鸭 大瓜咕 黑猫 Elena Miah Tuescany
搞什么啊
What the shit?!
前情提要
你挽回了我们的良好形象
You have restored a wholesome image.
■
校对：  负零     压制： 青鸟
董事会想让你担任七人队的联合队长
The board wants to make you cocaptain of The Seven.
我之前只是爱错了人
I am just a man who fell for the wrong woman.
我很期待能让大家看见真正的我
I am excited for everyone to meet the real me.
我和你们这些普通人不一样
I'm not just like the rest of you.
ShinY
深影
■
我更强大 我才是真的英雄
I am better! I'm the real hero.
白人男屌丝们爱死了你的发言
White males in the Rust Belt loved your speech.
屌爆了
Fuck yes!
他只是在下班回家的路上
He was just walking home from work.
就被蓝鹰狠狠地踩了一脚
Blue Hawk curb-stomped him so hard,
路面都被踩裂了
it cracked the pavement.
他们需要你去发声
They need you to speak up.
我是迈克尔·乔丹 不是马尔科姆·X
I'm Michael Jordan. I'm not Malcolm X.
ShinY
深影
我可以让好人加入七人队
I could bring good people into The Seven.
ShinY
深影
麻烦你保持距离 她是我的女朋友
You keep your distance. She's my girl now.
他真的疯了
He's lost his mind.
只要我还是执行总裁 他就没法乱来
As long as I'm CEO, he's under control.
纽曼就是爆头狂魔
Neuman's the head popper.
还算是斯坦·埃德加的女儿
Pretty much Stan Edgar's daughter, too.
我以为我们有能力
I thought we could fight Vought
和沃特一战 但是我们没有
the right way, but we can't.
我们得照你的方式来
We have to do it your way.
你应该对这个有兴趣
I think I have something.
B.C.L. RED是什么东西
What's B.C.L. RED?
某种武器
Some kind of weapon.
据传闻
If you believe the rumors,
就是它杀了士兵男孩
it's the thing that killed Soldier Boy.
要杀死祖国人 这是最好的机会
This is our best chance to kill Homelander.
这是什么 - 临时五号
- What's this? - Temp V.
能给你二十四小时的超能力
Makes you a Supe for 24 hours.
- 是什么杀了士兵男孩 - 去问中情局
- What killed Soldier Boy? - Ask the fucking CIA!
你一清二楚却只字不提
You knew and you never said a fucking word.
你说过你会一直照顾我的
You said you'd always watch out for me!
我恨你
I hate you.
安排我和小妮娜会面
Set up a meeting with Little Nina.
这可是个坏主意
This is a very bad idea.
你错了 弗兰基 这主意棒极了
No, Frenchie, it's a very fucking good idea.
我们要去俄罗斯了
We're going to Russia.
欢迎收看《劲歌金曲》
It's Solid Gold,
主持人玛丽莲·麦考
starring Marilyn McCoo.
本期表演者有歌手金·卡恩丝
With Solid Gold recording stars Kim Carnes,
橡树岭男孩乐队
the Oak Ridge Boys,
韦兰·弗劳尔斯与夫人
Waylan Flowers and Madame,
《劲歌金曲》的舞者们
the Solid Gold Dancers,
以及特别来宾士兵男孩
and very special guest Soldier Boy!
好吧 保持冷静
All right. Keep your hair on.
你用了V
You're on V.
临时五号
Temporary V.
只能持续二十四小时
Barely lasts 24 hours.
你从哪里弄到的
Where'd you even get it?
他们的网站上
One of them websites.
- 害我硬了好几天 - 别
- Boners for days. - No, no, no, no, no.
收起你的奸笑
None of your smirky shit.
我只打了一剂 好吗
I only had one dose. All right?
火药死了
Gunpowder's dead.
我们需要的情报也都到手了 结束了
We know what we need to know. End of.
等等 你
Wait, wait, you-you-you...
你杀了火药
you killed... Gunpowder?
用超能力吗
With powers? You...
你有超能力吗
You had superpowers?
好了 别说这个了 行吗
Oh, look, let's just give it a rest, all right?
药效结束了 我很好
It's over. I'm fine.
等下 其他人知道吗
Wait, wait, d-d-do the others know?
不 他们不知道
No, they do not.
要是你敢说出去 我就把你打到不省人事
And if they find out, I'll put you in a fucking coma.
对 你说的对
Yeah, no, you're right.
你确实精神很好
You seem t-totally fine.
《纽约时报》恶意抨击了你的生日直播
So, The New York Times viciously attacked your birthday telecast,
我引用一句他们的话
saying, and I quote,
看到这么强大的男子发狂的样子 令人害怕
"It's scary to see a man that strong that riled up."
没错 我确实很愤怒
Yeah, well, I am riled up. I am.
我受够了主流媒体堆砌的谎言
I am sick and tired of the lies peddled by the mainstream media.
听着 真正的问题是
Look, the real question here, Cam:
谁是抨击我的幕后主使
Who's behind these attacks?
谁想让我闭嘴
Who is trying to silence me?
或许是你在那场发言中提到的
Maybe the rich and powerful forces you mentioned
那些有钱有势的人 那可谓是勇气十足
in your, I thought, courageous speech.
- 谢谢 - 他们是谁
- Thank you. - Who are they?
他们中的大多数
Well, look, for the most part,
你们都闻所未闻
they're people you've never heard of,
但是他们躲在幕后操作
but they operate in the shadows,
他们才是控制局势的人
and they are the ones pulling the strings.
不幸的是 他们无处不在
And unfortunately, they're everywhere.
甚至沃特内部也有
Even inside of Vought.
抱歉 燕麦奶卖光了
Sorry, they were out of oat milk.
你来这里做什么
Uh, what are you doing here?
我不能心血来潮拜访一下吗
I can't drop by on a whim?
你从来不会心血来潮
You never do anything on a whim.
你是在开玩笑吧
You can't be serious.
我们不能追查祖国人
We never go after Homelander.
这是联邦政府的政策
It is practically federal policy.
这不是追查
No one is going after anyone.
只是委婉提醒一下谁才是老大
Just a gentle reminder of who's in charge.
我想你应该看了今早
I assume you saw him
他接受卡梅伦·科尔曼的访谈吧
on Cameron Coleman this morning?
他在试探我们的底线
He's testing boundaries.
有人这么做时 你就要给他们点教训
And when that happens, you have to discipline them
就像父母教训孩子
like, well, like a parent would.
就像你管教佐伊
Like with Zoe.
佐伊才不会让我死无全尸
Zoe won't rip my spine out.
别反应过度
Let's not overreact.
他在生日派对上大放厥词
He used foul language during that birthday rant.
你就发表公开声明
So you make a public statement.
严厉谴责 然后让委员会罚钱 小施惩戒
A stern reprimand, some FCC fines, nothing serious.
只是提醒他 他不能随心所欲
Just a reminder that he can't get away with anything.
他肯定高兴死了
He's gonna love that.
- 我们会保障你的安全 - 佐伊呢
- You'll be perfectly safe. - And Zoe?
尤其是佐伊
Especially Zoe.
祖国人可能会乱吠 但他不咬人
Homelander might bark a little, but he won't bite.
他还是会怕我
He's still afraid of me.
我绝不会让你和佐伊受到任何伤害
I would never let anything happen to you or Zoe.
你知道的 对吗
You know that, right?
当然
Yeah, yes, of course.
先生们
Gents.
你好啊
Hello, hello.
想必你就是妮娜
You must be Nina.
威廉·布彻
William Butcher.
塞尔盖 你怎么没告诉我 他竟然这么帅
Sergei, why you not tell me he's so delicious?
我在做俄罗斯饺子 要尝尝吗
I am making some pelmeni if you want.
当然 我的厨艺比不上塞尔盖
Of course, I cannot cook like my Sergei.
他做的法式炖锅
His cassoulet?
让我高潮了
Made me come.
我还是有点不高兴 你把他从我身边夺走
I'm still a bit upset you stole him from me.
他待在我们这儿好像更舒服 不是吗
Well, we offered him a better home, didn't we?
到底是什么风把你吹来了
So, to what do I owe this pleasure?
我在追查一种特殊的技术
I'm after a particular bit of tech.
一种武器 你肯定不陌生
A weapon, you'll not be surprised to hear.
我认为你和你克里姆林宫的朋友们
And I thought you and your mates at the Kremlin
或许能帮上忙
might be able to help.
你太抬举我了
That's giving me some credit.
别谦虚了 亲爱的
Where it's due, love.
我听说你拍下了影片
Way I heard it, you filmed a couple of punters
几个内政部的官员
from the Interior Ministry
在你的胯下尽情嬉戏
having a right old frolic under your golden shower.
这些足够还雪莉欠下的债
That's to cover Cherie's debt.
还有十万是你的辛苦费
Plus a hundred grand for your troubles.
中情局知道
Does your Bureau know
你把他们这些清白的钱给了我吗
you're giving me their nice clean money?
反正是美国政府给的
Well, it's the U.S. Government, love.
他们再印一些就行了
They'll just print more.
这些钱确实足够补偿我付出的辛苦
Yeah, the money is good for my trouble,
但是还有我遭受的痛苦和折磨呢
but what about my pain and suffering?
还有我花费的时间和受到的压力
Then there is the time spent and my stress.
我最近一直睡不好
I have been sleeping so poorly.
什么才能减轻你的痛苦
And what would ease your pain?
雪莉
Cherie.
不 不行
Non. No way.
我只要她
That is all I want.
我们的关系才刚刚开始
You and I, we're just getting started, dear love.
别告诉我 这里没有
Don't tell me there ain't no, uh...
回旋的余地
wiggle room.
- 布彻先生 - 弗兰基
- M'sieu Charcutier... - Frenchie.
是时候向全世界宣告
It's time we let the world know.
星光和我正在交往
Starlight and I are in love.
超话 祖国之光
#Homelight.
- 什么时候播出 - 今晚
- When's it air? - Um, tonight.
超话 祖国之光
#Homelight?
这个你也同意吗
You agreed to this?
就像你说的 休伊
It's like what you said, Hughie:
不惜一切代价
whatever it takes.
这就是
This is...
代价
This is what it takes.
你会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
真的
Really.
这次让我来救你
Let me save you for once.
休伊
Hughie.
这次一定要成功
This has to work.
一定有用
It'll work.
什么有用
What'll work?
我的沃特音速扬声器 它的设置
Uh, my VoughtSonic speaker setup.
不好意思 你怎么进来的
I'm sorry, uh, how did you get in?
我有钥匙
I have a key.
必须看好我的女朋友 对吧
Yeah, I got to keep an eye on my best girl, right?
顺便说一句 星光 你睡觉真沉
By the way, you're a sound sleeper, Starlight.
瞧你俩那表情
Oh, look at you two.
逗你们呢
I'm kidding.
来 高兴点
Come on, lighten up.
我就开个玩笑
I'm joking.
咱们真得走了 已经晚了
But we got to go. Running late.
去拍滚石杂志的封面 大热看点
Rolling Stone cover shoot. Hot Issue.
拍的时候要贴贴
We got "Hottest Ship."
别担心 休伊
Don't you worry, Hughie.
这点绯闻纯粹是为了做宣传
This little love affair is strictly for the cameras.
对了 当初梅芙也是这么开始的
Although that's how me and Maeve started out,
后来就太香艳了
and that got quite spicy.
真事 老弟
Yeah, I'm not kidding, man.
怎么说呢 梅芙不用上手就能
Let's just say that Maeve can bend a steel pipe
让梆硬的家伙软趴趴
without using her hands.
她怎么样
What's she like?
活儿好吗
She a good fuck?
动他一下 或者动他关心的人
Touch him or anyone he cares about,
我转身就走
and I'll walk.
也不再认可这个方案
And I'll take my approval points with me.
女人
Women.
小玩笑
I'm kidding.
你们真应该开心点
You really need to lighten up, guys.
快来吧 星光
Come on, Starlight.
马里奥还等着呢
Mario's waiting.
回头打给你
I'll call you later.
祝好 祖国人题
又是蓝鹰
Blue Hawk?
谁在乎蓝鹰的事
Who cares about Blue Hawk?
他和你的级别差太多了
He's way below your pay grade.
他在新泽西摧残黑人
He's brutalizing Black people in Trenton.
我觉得沃特有责任在这里表态
I think Vought has a responsibility here.
是吧
Right.
我去 你真这么想的啊
Wait, you're serious?
- 我就是想找他聊聊 - 必须的
- I just want to talk to him. - Of course.
我们特别注重社会公正
Social justice is so important around here.
- 是吗 什么时候开始的 - 火车头
- Since when? - A-Train,
我非常欣赏黑人的命也是命这句流行语
"Black Lives Matter" Is my favorite hashtag.
我的Insta 只用黑屏
My Insta? Nothing but black screens.
看你多出彩啊
And look at you. You look amazing!
你带来了崭新的操作
This whole new thing you did,
为整个活动激发活力
that is exactly what inspired this entire campaign.
沉默意味着沆瀣一气
To be silent is to be complicit.
咱先拍照
So let's shoot the spot,
回头再聊蓝鹰的事
and we'll chat about Blue Hawk later.
具体什么时候 艾希莉
When, Ashley?
回头就聊 火车头
Later, A-Train.
摄影车开拍
And action on Dolly.
我们为了和平 爱和繁荣走到一起
We're here today for peace and love and prosperity!
他们这是要去哪里
Where all those people going?
上街抗议
There's a protest down the street.
火车头 你去哪里 马上就开拍了
A-Train, where you going? Almost ready to shoot.
我有重要的事
This is important.
我们要聆听彼此的心声
We got to listen to each other.
多喝火车头强力功能饮料
A-Train's Turbo Rush Energy Drink.
大概还要四五天吧
Like, uh, four or five days maybe.
你骑动感单车摔了 竟然要歇一礼拜
A hell of a week to fall off your Peloton.
真的 我吃止疼药就跟吃口香糖似的
Look, I'm popping Vicodin like they're Tic Tacs,
胳膊疼死了
and my arm still kills.
我去上班也没用 维琪
Uh, I'm no good to you, Vicky.
- 对吧 - 那行吧
- Really. - Fine. Okay.
好好躺着 多休息 养好伤
Just stay in bed, get some rest, get better.
我正卧床养伤呢
That's exactly what I'm doing.
谢了 维琪
Thanks, Vick.
小子 头一次做私人飞机吗
First time flying private, kid?
头一次出国
First time out of the country.
五年呐 我给妮娜干了二十三单
Five years, I work for Nina, 23 contracts.
她就从来没犒劳过什么
Never she's giving anything away.
这什么情况
What is this?
让咱们坐飞机 还崭新的护照
Now she giving us the plane, those shiny passports?
你说他是不是要把雪莉交给她
You think he promised her Cherie?
去死吧 弗兰基
Fucking hell, Frenchie.
你真以为我禽兽不如吗
What kind of monster do you think I am, eh?
放轻松
Enjoy.
就当自己是大佬的跟班
Pretend you're on Entourage.
屌什么屌
Merde.
有钱人都是蠢货和狗日的
Entourage is but for the stupid and the damned.
你好
Hi.
能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
- 不行 - 梅芙 别这样
- No. - Maeve, please.
你不是不训练了吗
I heard that you stopped training.
是吗
Yeah?
你还听说我一礼拜有六天喝大酒
You also hear that I wake up six days a week hungover,
光着膀子跟一堆人群交吧
tits-deep in some random fuck pile?
都是假象
People think what I want them to.
行吧 我想问问
Okay, listen.
你听说过有个什么B.C.L.红吗
Have you ever heard of something called "B.C.L. RED"?
你说那种能弄死祖国人的武器
You mean a weapon that can kill Homelander,
你想问 布彻能不能找到吧
if Butcher can find it?
你知道
You know?
你以为他们从哪里得到的追查线索
Who do you think sent them down the rabbit hole?
所以我才不断训练
It's why I'm training.
四个月滴酒不沾 吃些难以下咽的健康食品
Or haven't had a drink in four awful, shit-eating months.
我没准还能帮布彻多争取点时间
Maybe I can buy Butcher a second or two
最后完美一击
to get a good shot.
起码到时候我也能出手帮忙
At the very least, I'll get a couple of licks in.
这样啊
Okay.
那行 现在有你 有我
Okay, okay. So there's you and me.
是不是能再找几个
Maybe we can find some others.
说得对
Right. Yeah.
我觉得你和全能的德卢斯联手
I'm sure you and Duluth's Most Mighty
就有足够的实力搞定这件事
would really get the job done.
该由我来解决这个问题
This is my problem.
谁让我曾经和这个混蛋好过呢
I'm the one who was with the asshole.
梅芙...
Maeve...
你不能单枪匹马地面对
you cannot do this alone.
他会杀死你
He'll kill you.
你真的完全不考虑自己的安危吗
You really care that little about yourself?
我自作自受
I got it coming.
好消息
Good news.
妮娜和她在克里姆林宫的碎催聊过
Nina's had a word with her Kremlin piss boys,
找到实验室在哪里了
and she's located the lab.
- 太好了 在哪里 - 要让她说
- That's great. Where is it? - Before she tells us that,
咱们就得先帮她干点小活
we just got to do a little job for her.
不是什么大事
Ain't nothing.
替她对付一个这里的地头蛇
Just some local oligarch who got in her bad books.
不行 我不干这种买卖
Non. I don't do this anymore.
肯定不能给妮娜干
Definitely not for Nina.
正好 这么个好差事 是吧
Well, that's a good job, then, innit?
还用不着你动手
'Cause you're not the one doing it.
让她干
She is.
不好意思了 美女 能者多劳呗
Sorry, love, victim of your own success.
计划是妮娜送你进去
Now, Nina's got you in.
假装给那精虫上脑的货提供服务
You'll be the wanker's pro girl for the night.
你只要进去 把那厮废了
You just get in there, give the cunt a good noose,
拍拍屁股走人 轻松啊
and get the fuck out. Easy-peasy.
求你了 别让她去
I'm begging you, no.
我说弗兰基 要么干 要么雪莉人头落地
Look, Frenchie, it was this or Cherie's head.
这太扯了 好人没好报啊
Fucking hell. No good deed.
我他妈不是你的杀人工具
你还就是
That is exactly what you are.
你俩搞不清楚情况了...
And case you two forgot...
...我让你们干什么...
...I tell you what to do...
...你们就他妈干什么
...and you fucking do it.
我去 你这是又要跟我说
Oh, shit. You're about to tell me
特别吓人的事了吧
something awful again, aren't you?
好好听我说
Just listen to me.
如果这就是最后的解决方案...
If it comes down to it...
我是说如果我们必须和他正面对抗
I mean, if we need to fight him for real,
你会帮我吗
will you help me?
你说真的
You serious?
就冲他最近的种种表现
With how he's been acting lately?
他可是不可战胜的
He's invincible.
应该有办法 明白吗
There might be a way. Okay?
不告诉你具体情况 才能让你更安全
It's safer if you don't know how,
但我们需要你的帮助
but we need your help.
这里有我 有梅芙
There's me. There's Maeve.
我们还需要再找四 五个人
We probably need four or five more,
我们有机会赢
and we have a shot.
对不起 阿莱克斯
I'm so sorry, Alex.
我原本不想拉你干这个
I didn't want to have to ask you this,
但我真不知道还能找谁
but I don't know where else to go.
那行 我干了
Okay, I'm in.
你干了
You're in?
这么简单
Just like that?
你就不用再好好考虑下
You don't even want to think about it?
我想好了
I'm good.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你为什么对我这么...
Why are you so...
这么好
nice to me?
这还不够明显吗
Isn't it obvious?
你是我唯一爱过的女孩 安妮·詹纽艾瑞
You're the only girl I've ever loved, Annie January.
这个嘛 阿莱克斯 不好意思 我...
Oh. Alex, I'm sorry. I-I-I...
这不行 因为我和休伊...
No, it's just me and Hughie...
我逗你玩呢
I'm fucking with you.
别这么自恋
Get over yourself.
你不会真以为我奶奶能让我娶一个
You really think my grandmother was gonna let me marry
你这么彻底的白人姑娘吧
the whitest girl in all of white?
你太混蛋了
You asshole.
我是小混蛋行了吧 现在听我说
Yes, that's what I am. Listen to me.
自从你搬到纽约之后 你变得特别坚强
Since you moved to New York, you've gotten tough as shit.
那个我认识的安妮
The Annie I knew?
她能看到人们心中的善
She saw the good in people.
我帮助你是因为这是正确的事情
I'm gonna help you 'cause it's the right thing to do.
仅此而已
That's all.
欢迎加入 超音速
Welcome aboard, Supersonic.
我们很高兴有你加入
We're all so pleased to have you here.
尤其是你之前的爱人 星光
Especially your former lover, Starlight.
看在你的面子上 准备了一些小惊喜
So, in your honor, got a little surprise.
说真的 我们这座大楼里的
Mm. Seriously, we have the best taco bowls
墨西哥玉米卷做的最好了
right here in the building.
会让你有种宾至如归的感觉 朋友
Should make you feel right at home, pal.
欢迎回来 孩子
Bienvenidos, muchacho.
我不说西班牙语 先生
I, uh, I don't really speak Spanish, sir.
这些太美味了
This is muy delicioso.
好了
Okay.
会议结束
Meeting is over.
我需要这个房间 都走吧
And I need the room, so away we go.
事实上 祖国人 我有些事情要说
Um, actually, Homelander, I've got something.
火车头
A-Train.
当然可以了
By all means.
说吧
Floor's yours.
我想谈谈有关蓝鹰的事
I wanted to talk about Blue Hawk.
蓝鹰
Blue Hawk?
特伦顿的
Out of Trenton.
好吧 怎么了
Okay. What?
他一直在在黑人社区里过度巡逻
He's been over-patrolling Black neighborhoods.
这是个问题
It's a problem.
这太糟了
That's terrible.
谢谢 星光 这的确是
Thank you, Starlight. It is.
我想着 自从我们
I thought, you know, since we got...
想在宣传片里重塑形象
...some rebuilding to do in that demo,
也许我们可以让他做一段时间的冷板凳
maybe we could bench him for a while.
可以
Could be
在非裔美国群体中
a six-, seven-point bump
至少提升六到七点的支持率
with African Americans, at least.
等等 你想让他停职
Wait, you want to bench him?
我们不是需要更多的超级英雄 而不是裁员吗
Don't we need... more superheroes, not less?
你和蓝鹰有很多的相似之处
I mean, you share a lot of the same base as Blue Hawk.
你真的可以对犯罪表现得如此温和吗
Can you really afford to look soft on crime?
你说得对 深海
That's actually correct, Deep.
干得好
Good job.
这就是你的答案 真不走运啊 火车头
There's your answer. So, bad luck, A-Train, huh?
好了 我需要这个房间 都出去
Okay. I do need the room. Out.
怎么了
What?
维多利亚·纽曼今晚会举办一场新闻发布会
Victoria Neuman is doing a press conference tonight.
所以呢
So?
是关于你的
It's about you.
你现在才发现吗
You're just finding out about it now?
我敢肯定这只是虚张声势罢了
I'm sure it's a nothingburger.
嘿 过来一下
Hey, come here for a sec.
你的白痴大脑被傻X日了吗
Is your idiot brain getting fucked by stupid?
这不是反问句
It's not rhetorical.
回答我
Answer me.
没有
No.
我的白痴大脑没有
My idiot brain is not
- 被傻X日 先生 - 那好
- getting fucked by stupid, sir. - Well, then go
去做你唯一的工作 然后弄清
and do your only job and find out
发生了什么 艾希莉
what the fuck is going on, Ashley.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
深海
Deep.
谁问 不好意思 谁问你了
Who asked... Excuse me. Who asked you?
刚才 谁问你的意见了
Back there. Who the fuck asked you for your opinion?
- 我是这个小组的一员 - 拜托
- I am a member of this team. - Please.
祖国人是个伟大的人
Homelander's a great man,
但你这拍他马屁的方式
but the way that you kiss his ass
真恶心
is fucking gross.
嘿 老兄 听着 我明白
Hey, man. Look, I get it.
好吗 这很难接受
Okay? This is tough.
我 亲自被祖国人选中
You know, me handpicked by Homelander
重新归队 而你 又走上了出局的路
to come back and you on your way out again.
现在想着重塑形象是不是太晚了
And a rebrand. Oh, this late in the game.
全新的火车头
Ouch. The new A-Train.
鹰射手转形成鹰说唱
How'd that work out for Eagle the Archer
那次怎么样来着 哦 对了
when he became Eagle the Rapper? Oh, that's right.
那次没成 真可惜啊 兄弟
It fucking didn't. It's just sad, man.
你就像是阿什顿·库彻日了一条小丑鱼
You're like if Ashton Kutcher fucked a clown fish.
你就是个笑话 还这么蠢
You're a joke, and you're so dumb
自己却一无所知
you don't even know it.
真的吗 好吧 不如我告诉祖国人是谁泄露了
Oh, yeah? Well, how 'bout I tell Homelander who really leaked
风暴是纳粹这件事的
all that Nazi shit on Stormfront?
不如我告诉他是你在大西洋里
How 'bout I tell him you fished the Flight 37 video
找到了三十七号航班的录像并把它交给了梅芙
out of the Atlantic and gave it to Maeve?
什么 来吧 冲向我啊 兄弟
What? Come on. Run at me, bro.
我忘了你的腿不好使了
I forgot your legs don't fucking work.
你打了我的腮
Gill-punch me?
- 没错 - 混蛋
- Yeah. - Motherfucker.
伙计们 伙计们
Boys, boys, boys.
火车头
A-Train.
待在这里休息一下那两条无用的腿吧
Just stay there and rest those useless fucking legs.
嘿 老兄
Hey, man.
- 别这么做 别这么做 - 放开我
- Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. - Get off of me!
你不想这么做的 放松
You do not want to do that. Take it easy.
冷静一下
Calm down,
- 好吗 冷静一下 兄弟 - 滚开
- all right? Take it easy, man. - Fuck off.
去他的
Fuck him.
去祖国
Fuck Home.
别说了
Stop.
万一他听见了呢
What if he hears you?
我就该受深海的气吗
I'm supposed to take shit from the Deep?
他妈的深海
The fucking Deep?
祖国人支持他不支持我
Homelander's gonna back him over me?
在我为了他鞠躬尽瘁之后
After everything that I've done for that man.
我就经历了一次挫折
I hit one little speed bump.
现在
Now...
我就是个垃圾了
I'm fucking garbage.
如果
What if...
我们可以做些什么呢
...we could do something about it?
你有什么想法
What do you have in mind?
布彻 你怎么了
Butcher, what the fuck
伙计
is wrong with you, man?
不如你来告诉我 我怎么了
I'm sure you're gonna tell me.
你对瑞恩做出那种混事
That shit you pulled with Ryan
现在又对山崎纪说出这种冷漠无情的话
and now this coldhearted shit you said to Kimiko?
怎么会有人变成这样一个彻头彻尾的混蛋
How could anybody be such a complete asshole?
- 练习 - 你敲响了
- Practice. - You knocked
我家的门 混蛋
on my doorstep, motherfucker.
我服从指挥 但这
And I respect the chain of command, but this?
我不会再忍受你的这些混账事了 兄弟
I'm not gonna tolerate your bullshit anymore, man.
你记得我们初次见面的场景吗
Do you remember when we met?
记忆犹新
Hard to forget.
我和上校 我们挑选下属
Me and the colonel, we had our pick of officers.
有些
Some, uh...
有些没入选
Some real haircuts.
你有没有想过
Do you ever wonder
为什么我们选择了一个低等的海军陆战队士兵
why we picked some grunt Marine stuck in the brig?
想想看
Let's see.
我干翻了我那种族主义的指挥官 就一拳
I knocked out my racist C.O. Sent him to the ICU
就把他送进了重症监护室 所以我很强壮
with one punch, so you knew I was strong.
你们还看了我的档案
And you read my file,
所以你们知道我痛恨沃特
so you knew I hated Vought.
没错 但你说的一个也不对
Yeah, it weren't none of them.
它们的确是优势 但是不是我们选你的原因
I mean, they didn't hurt, mind, but no.
我们跟那些和你
We spoke to the blokes
一起做过基础训练的人谈了谈
that you went through basic with.
对于你 他们说
And to the man, they said
你是那个能把整个排凝聚在一起的人
that you were the one that held that platoon together.
一个天生的领袖
A natural-born leader.
你从来没跟我说过这个
You never told me that.
伙计
Mate,
我对自己有着清醒的认识
I'm under no illusions about who I am.
这就是为什么我拉你入伙的原因
And that's why we brought you in.
无论我变得多么冷酷无情
'Cause no matter how hard I got to be...
你都会在这里照顾黑袍纠察队
...you're here to look after the Boys.
现在
Now,
如果我想照顾他们
if I thought to do that,
我就不能成为一个彻头彻尾的混蛋
I can't be a complete asshole,
对吗
can I?
只能差不多
Just mostly one.
伊瑞娜 对吧
Irina, yes?
你迟到了
You're late.
来吧
Come on.
女士们
Ladies...
现在 最有意思的部分来了
And now, for the most delicious part.
这些是违禁品
These are contraband.
祖国人的"星条旗屌"
Homelander's "Star-spangled Banger."
深海的"比目鱼杵"
The Deep "Flounder Pounder."
玄色的"无声尖叫者"
Black Noir's "Silent Screamer."
选一个吧
Choose.
来吧
Come.
Come on.
脱掉裙子
Take off your dress.
手和膝盖着地
On your hands and knees...
你的朋友会
...and your friend will
- 感觉怎么样 - 想吐
- How do you feel? - Like throwing up.
记住 是他罪有应得
Just remember, he deserves this.
祝你好运 亲爱的
Good luck, sport.
下午好 感谢大家齐聚在这里
Good afternoon. Thank you all for being here.
我是国会女议员维多利亚·纽曼
I'm Congresswoman Victoria Neuman, the director of
- 联邦超人类事务局局长 - 怎么了
- the Federal Bureau of Superhuman Affairs. - What's going on?
- 该死 - 过去的一年里 我局一直在
- Oh, shit. - For the last year, the Bureau has been working
一个指导原则下与沃特国际进行合作
with Vought International under one guiding principle.
那就是
That.
我们中的最强大的人不能凌驾于法律之上
The most powerful among us are not above the law,
包括公司内最有权势的人
including the most powerful man at the company.
祖国人
Homelander...
作为吹哨人勇敢地站了出来
...has bravely come forward as a whistleblower
提交了沃特公司执行总裁
and provided evidence of crimes
斯坦·埃德加在公司内部实施
committed within Vought
犯罪的证据
by CEO Stan Edgar.
在接下来的日子里
And in the coming days,
联邦超人类事务局将会调查针对埃德加先生
the FBSA will be investigating
涉及敲诈勒索
charges of blackmail,
做伪证和妨碍司法公正
perjury and obstruction of justice
的相关指控
against Mr. Edgar.
沃特国际必须要坚守
Vought International must be held
最高道德标准和法律标准
to the highest ethical and legal standards.
- 你做了什么 - 民众有权知道关于
- What did you do? - The people are entitled to the truth
他们的英雄们的真相
about their heroes...
我很早之前就该做的事情
Something I should've done a long time ago.
这是一家超英公司 一直如此
This is a superhero company.
公司属于我们 不是他
Always has been. Belongs to us, not him.
所以我让事情回到正轨了
So I set things straight.
就是这样
That's all.
多说一句
Oh, and, uh,
不论之前谁在他的庇护之下
anyone who's been hiding behind his little apron?
现在都结束了
That's over now, too.
要天下大变了 各位
It's a new day, people.
这是七人队的黎明
It's The Dawn of The Seven.
为什么
Why?
这些年来 不是你在保护我
All these years, you weren't protecting me.
是我在保护你
I was protecting you.
- 我必须得照顾佐伊 - 我们得走了
- I have to look out for Zoe. - We need to go,
埃德加先生
Mr. Edgar.
从现在开始 谈话重点
So, from now on, the talking points
不再由苏珊负责 而是由我负责
don't come from Suzanne. They come from me.
我要审核文案中的每个用词
I approve every single word of copy.
我说清楚了吗
Are we clear?
- 非常 女士 - 天啊
- Crystal, ma'am. - Jesus Christ.
这稿子看上去跟一屋子
It's like this script was written by a roomful
红屁股猴儿写得一样 对吧
of chapped-ass monkeys, am I right?
写得太差了
It's so bad.
这是我写的 女士
I wrote it, ma'am.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你的白痴大脑是被傻X日了吗
Is your idiot brain getting fucked by stupid?
这不是反问句
No, that's not rhetorical.
回答我
Answer me.
我要是说呢
What if I said yes?
那我就不得不惩罚你了
Then I would have to punish you.
你要怎么惩罚我呢
How would you punish me?
我的白痴大脑是被傻X日了 女士
My idiot brain is getting fucked by stupid, ma'am.
你进展如何
Well, how'd you get on?
妮娜会喜欢看到这个的
Oh, Nina's gonna love this.
看 我告诉你了
See? Told you.
小菜一碟
Easy-peasy.
我不能再做下去了
I can't do this.
甜心
Mon coeur?
那些女孩儿
Those girls...
向你开枪的那些
The girls who shot you?
她们只是害怕了
They were just scared.
我知道 我不怪她们
I know, I don't blame them.
她们和我一样
They were bought and sold
被随意买卖
same as me.
布彻
Butcher
卖掉我
sold me.
他不把我们当成人看
He doesn't treat any of us as people.
布彻
Butcher
闪光
Shining Light
小妮娜
Little Nina.
他们都一样
They are the same.
我们只有彼此
We only have each other.
你
It's you
和我
and me.
你是对的
You're right.
我们是时候该离开了
Maybe it's time we leave.
- 真的吗 - 真的
- Really? - Really.
什么时候
When?
布彻 他...
Well, Butcher, he can, uh...
去他妈的
Well, he can lick my asshole.
但休伊
But Hughie
和马文 他们需要我们
and, uh, and M.M., they need us.
所以我们完成这次的任务
So we do this job.
你之后想去哪里呢
And then where do you want to go?
马赛
Marseilles.
我们就去马赛
We go to Marseilles.
嗨
Hey.
今天经血量大
Heavy flow day?
开玩笑的
Kidding.
说实话
Be honest.
你想要射爆我得脑袋吗
You thinking of popping my melon?
谁知道呢 试一试呗
Who knows? Give it a whirl?
能长话短说么
Can we make this quick?
今天我挺累的
It's been a long day.
确实
It has.
当众重击那样的老男人并不容易
It can't have been easy shanking the old man like that.
如果能让你感到些许安慰的话
But, if it's any consolation,
他也打算对你做一样的事
he was ready to do exactly the same to you.
这是什么
What's this?
不过是我从埃德加的办公室
Just a little oppo research
借来的一点竞争对手的报告
that I borrowed from Edgar's office.
你猜我是怎么发现你是我们中的一员的
How do you think I found out you were one of us?
这不是他的 是别人的
This isn't his. This is someone else's.
不
No.
是他的
It's his.
你不是他女儿
You're not his daughter.
你是他的武器
You're his weapon.
他们就做这种事儿
It's what they do.
他们都一样
They all do it.
全部的人
All of them.
但 事情的关键在于
Look, the point is,
他们不得不对我们做这些
they have to do that to us.
他们不得不 因为他们知道
They have to, because they know
他们晚上睡不着的时候....
deep down when they lie awake at night...
你带来了吗
Do you have it or not?
正如承诺的一样
As promised.
原始配方 配料齐全
Original recipe. All 11 herbs and spices.
维琪
Vicky.
很高兴你选择了你的种族
I'm glad you chose your own kind.
这很明智
That was smart.
布彻 我能...
Butcher, can I, uh...
你在做什么
What are you doing?
应急措施
Contingency.
以防实验室的事情出了岔子
In case things go ass over tit at the lab.
我想要试一试
I want to try some.
别发癫了
Don't be daft.
这玩意是毒药 休伊
This shit is poison, Hughie.
像你这样的小伙子不该碰
A lad like you don't want no part of it.
像我这样的失败者
What, you mean like a loser?
蠢货吗
A fuckup?
祖国人迟早会找到瑞安
Sooner or later, Homelander will find Ryan.
只是时间问题
Okay? It's just a matter of time.
我不得不注射 好吧
I have to do this, all right?
你不必如此
You don't.
安妮同样也一样危险
Annie's in just as much danger.
祖国人差点当着她的面把我切成两半
Homelander almost lasered me in half in front of her,
而且 这感觉就和 就和
and it was like... it was like I was back
我被霸凌时一样 不得不忍气吞声
with every bully that I ever had, just taking it.
她不得不再次出手救我
And then she had to save me again.
布彻 求你了 求你了
Butcher, please. Please.
求你了
Please.
因为现在 我快气到不能呼吸了
Because right now, I am so angry that I can't even breathe.
休伊
Oh, Hughie.
有它更糟
It's shittier.
这不是力量
It's not power.
是惩罚
It's punishment.
不该由你这样的人承受
You don't deserve none of it.
你就活该承受吗
What, and you do?
准备出发
Get ready to go.
你这里的风景真是不错
You do have a hell of a view from up here.
我不得不承认
I'll give you that.
你应该从空中看看
You should see it from space.
难以置信 八十对六十
Unbelievable. Eighty over 60.
你的一生都要崩塌了
Your entire life is imploding,
你跟约翰·格里森姆的小说角色一样
and it's as if you're reading fucking John Grisham.
我听说你
I heard about your, uh,
暂时离职休假了
temporary leave of absence, by the way.
不过暂时休假确实容易变成
Those things do have a nasty habit
永久休假 不是吗
of becoming permanent, though, don't they?
- 别怪维琪... 你 - 我不怪她
- Don't blame Vicky. You... - I don't.
如果说有什么事儿是我教给她的
If there's one thing I taught her,
那就是如何八面玲珑
it was to play all sides.
她比我认为的更像我
She's more like me than I ever imagined.
但我很好奇
But I am curious.
你到底给了她什么
What did you give her?
一点儿尊重 斯坦
A little respect, Stan.
你本该给我的东西
Something you should've given me.
有什么用
What good would that do?
尊重对你有用吗
Where would it even go
如果你那空虚的灵魂
but to the bottomless, gaping pit of insecurity
充满不安
you call a soul?
天 你知道吗
Oh, God. You want to know something?
我过去特别害怕你
I used to be intimidated by you.
我承认
I did.
但现在看到你 我...
And now I look at you, I-I'm just...
我不知道当时为什么怕你 真的
I-I have no idea why. Truly.
你甚至算不上差劲
Y...You're not even pathetic.
你什么都不是啊
You're...you're just... nothing.
那为什么你还站在这
Then why are you still here,
仿佛我是你爸一样 拼命寻求我的认可
looking for my approval like I'm your daddy?
就算我是 你有什么需要我认可的吗
And even if I were, what would there be to approve of?
公司是你的了
The company is yours.
没人能反抗你了
No one left to stand up to you.
但我想你会非常后悔的
But I think you'll come to sorely regret that.
为什么呢
And why is that?
因为也没人能掩护你了
Because there's no one left to cover for you, either.
最终 也许很快
Eventually, probably soon,
世界就会意识到
the world will recognize you
你是个多么可怜的令人失望的人
for the pitiful disappointment you are.
你不值得我尊敬
You are not worthy of my respect.
你也不是神
You are not a god.
你只是个糟糕的产品
You are simply bad product.
我很害怕
I'm scared.
我知道
I know.
我小时候 他们也对我做过同样的事
You know, when I was little, they did the same thing to me.
但我没事
And I'm all right.
我们必须这么做 好吗
We have to, okay?
因为你知道吗 它会让你
'Cause you know what? It's gonna make you
永远变得强大
so strong and safe.
和安全
Forever.
- 好吗 - 好
- Okay? - Okay.
好吧 转身 趴下
Okay, turn around. On your belly.
会有一点疼
Just a pinch.
好了 过来
Okay. Okay. Come here, come here, come here.
没事的
It's okay. Shh.
没事的 没事的
It's okay. It's okay. Shh.
没事的
Shh, shh. It's okay.
会没事的
- Ow! - It's gonna be okay.
没事的
Shh, shh. It's okay.
我在呢 我在呢
I've got you. I've got you. Shh.
那个叫妮娜的小妞没帮我们
That chick Nina didn't do us no favors.
这不是实验室 是一个军事基地
That ain't a lab. It's a military compound.
抢劫俄罗斯的军事基地
Russian military compound.
就跟抢劫鲜果店一样
Be like storming a Baja Fresh.
鲜果店可不会用全自动的
Baja Fresh ain't shooting us
Ak-47射我们 混蛋
with AK-47s on full auto, motherfucker.
赤色黎明 混蛋
Red Dawn, motherfucker.
洛奇四 混蛋
Rocky IV, motherfucker.
快点
Come on.
我们时间不多
We ain't got much time.
知道这把超级枪
Any idea what this Supe gun is
- 长什么样吗 - 自己发现不是更有趣吗
- supposed to look like? - Ain't the joy in the discovery, eh?
这是什么
What is it?
嘿 这有东西
Hey, there's something here.
看
Look.
快看
Look, look. Oh.
嘿
Hey.
写的什么
What does it say?
他的名字叫杰米
Says his name is Jamie.
杰米
Jamie.
嗨
Hi.
- 你还好吗 杰米 - 别逗它了
- Are you okay, Jamie? - No, no, no, don't fuck with it.
别管他了
Just leave him alone.
噢 杰米
Aw. Jamie.
这只帅气小巧的小沙鼠是谁啊
Who's a handsome, petite, little gerbil?
这是只仓鼠
It's a hamster.
我女儿养过三只
My daughter went through three of them.
糟了
Oh, shit.
该死的五号剂仓鼠
Motherfucking V'd-up hamster.
我告诉过你
I told you
别惹他 该死的
not to fuck with him. Goddamn it.
精神点啊
Look lively!
谢了 杰米
Merci, Jamie.
我没子弹了
I'm out!
喂
Oi!
晚上好啊 讨厌鬼们
Evening, cunts.
马文
M.M.!
噢
Oh! Oh!
该死的 抱歉
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你的鸡巴露出来了
Your dick's out.
- 布彻 - 好吧 听着 等一下
- Butcher? - All right, all right, look, hang about.
你和休伊都用了化合物V吗
You and Hughie both took Compound V?
你们俩也是他妈的超人类了吗
What are you two, fucking Supes now?
临时V
Temporary V.
她说 你们为什么要故意对自己这样
Oh, she say, "Why do you do this to yourself on purpose?"
只持续二十四小时 好吗
Only lasts 24 hours, all right?
紧急情况下救急用的
Break glass in case of emergencies, you know,
- 比如现在 - 你把这个给休伊了吗
- like this one. - And you give this to-to Hughie?
我没有给他 肯定是他这个小偷
I didn't give it to him. The thieving git must have broken
撬开箱子自己偷的
broken into the case and nicked it.
- 嗯 - 我们先找到东西
- Uh... - Let's just find this thing
然后他妈的离开这里 好吗
and get the fuck out of here, all right?
你不该自暴自弃 孩子
You're better than this, kid.
布彻
Butcher, I'm... Look...
我很抱歉 好吗 只是我
I'm s... I'm sorry, okay? It's just, I...
士兵男孩
Soldier Boy.
没事的
Ah... It's okay.
山崎纪
Kimiko.
没事的
It's okay. Huh?
It's okay.
她伤口没愈合
She's not healing.
为什么她的伤口没愈合
Why she's not healing?
山崎纪 为什么她的伤口不愈合
Kimiko. Why does she not heal?
山崎纪 她的伤口不愈合了
Kimiko. She's not healing!
纱布 弗兰基 新纱布
Gauze. Frenchie, fresh gauze.
- 不 - 给我一些新纱布 睁开眼睛
- Oh, no, no, no... - Give me some fresh gauze. Open your eyes.
睁开你的眼睛 抬起她的头 弗兰基
Open your eyes. Hold her head up, Frenchie.
- 亲爱的 - 睁开眼睛 山崎纪
- Mon coeur. - Open your eyes, Kimiko.
- 嘿 - 睁开眼睛 睁开你的眼睛
- Hey. - Open your eyes. Open your eyes.
- 亲爱的 - 山崎纪 就是这样
- Mon coeur. - Kimiko, there you go.
看着弗兰基
Look at Frenchie.
- 亲爱的 - 睁开眼睛 山崎纪
- Mon coeur? Mon coeur? - Open your eyes, Kimiko,
睁开眼睛
open your eyes.
士兵男孩一直都是个难搞的混蛋
Soldier Boy was always an hard bastard,
- 但从没那样过 - 亲爱的
- but not like that. - Mon coeur.
他们肯定对他做了什么
They must have done something to him.
你觉得是什么
What you think?
亲爱的
Mon coeur. Mon coeur.
- 山崎纪 - 结束了 布彻
- Kimiko... - It's over, Butcher.
我再也没有团队要维系了
There ain't no team for me to hold together no more.
亲爱的
Mon coeur?
不 求你了 不
No, please, please, no, no, no, no, no.
是你搞成这样的
You made sure of that.
拜托 山崎纪
Come on. Come on. Kimiko!
抬起她的头 弗兰基
Hold her head up, Frenchie.
- 她 不 - 山崎纪 睁开眼睛
- She's... No. - Kimiko, open your eyes.
- 亲爱的 - 睁开眼睛
- Mon coeur! - Open your eyes.
你知道吗 我想飞回家
Hey, you know what? I think I want to fly home.
你想飞吗
You want to fly?
车就在这呢
Uh, the car's right here.
下次吧
Um, next time?
不 来吧 我会抱你的
No, no, no, no. Come on, I'll-I'll carry you.
谁想看星光和我一起飞
Who wants to see Starlight and me fly?
你要让他们失望吗
What, are you gonna disappoint them?
- 好吧 - 来吧 上来
- Okay. - Come on, up you go.
这就对了
There you go.
我很想带你去看一个美景
I, uh, I have a view I really want to show you.
会让你大吃一惊的
It's gonna blow your mind.
抓紧了
Hold on tight.
这座城市真美
This really is a beautiful city.
你不需要这样做了
You know, you don't need to do this.
没摄像机在拍了
The cameras are gone.
是的
Yeah.
但你看 这就是我的特点 星光
But, see, that's the thing about me, Starlight.
如果我承诺了什么 就会兑现
If I promise something, I deliver.
那边就是一生难忘的美景
Now, that is the view of a lifetime.
阿莱克斯
Alex?
Alex!
我的天
Oh, my God.
你他妈的神经病
You fucking psycho!
别这样 你知道结果会怎样的
Stop it. You know how that ends.
再说
You know, besides,
你跟我一样都有错
this is your fault as much as it is mine.
- 什么 - 火车头告诉我你们两个想叛变
- What? - A-Train told me about you two mutineers
还有你们的小阴谋
and your little plot.
你就是不明白 是吗
You just don't get it, do you?
我是说 你他妈的根本不了解
I mean, you have no fucking grasp
你现在的处境 对吗
of the situation you're in at all, right?
我再解释一遍
I'm gonna break it down one more time,
我会说得一清二楚
and I'm gonna make it crystal clear
这样连你都能理解了 好吗
so that even you can understand it, okay?
不会再有什么阴谋 计划 胡闹了
There will be no more plotting, planning, playing around.
都结束了 知道么
That is over, okay?
从现在开始 就只有我忠实的 亲爱的
From here on out, there is only my dutiful, loving
女友星光 崇拜我 而且只崇拜我
main squeeze Starlight, worshiping me and me alone.
因为如果你稍有不慎
Because if you step one inch out of line,
我是说 如果你他妈的眨错了眼
I mean, I-if you so much as fucking blink the wrong way,
那么那边 亲爱的 就会是休伊了
then that, my love, will be Hughie.
这次你明白了吗
Do you understand this time?
很好
Good.
那就说出来 这样我才知道
Then say it, so I know.
那就会是休伊了
"That'll be Hughie."
That'll be Hughie.
这就对了
There it is.
自己想办法回家吧
Find your own way home.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现